Post Office Arbitration Files 5739
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Post Office Arbitration Files
1971-1984
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jensen, Vernon H.
5739
8 cubic feet
8 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5699389
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 30, 1989
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Scope and Contents
These arbitration files are coded to indicate what is included in the file: TR = Transcript(s) B = Brief EX = Exhibit(s) AN = Arbitrator's Notes RC = Routine Correspondence A = Agreement SD = Supporting Document(s)
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5269: United National Association of Post Office Craftsmen Records 5839: Vernon Jenson Additional Arbitration Files
Hours of labor.; Grievance arbitration.; Insubordination.; Violence in the workplace.; Absenteeism (Labor); Alcoholism and employment.; Occupations -- Classification; Drugs and employment.; People with disabilities -- Employment; Postal service -- Employees -- Salaries, etc; Sick leave.; Strikes and lockouts.; Tardiness.; Employees -- Dismissal of; Work environment.; Vacations, Employee.; Postal service -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; Jensen, Vernon H.; United States Postal Service.; American Postal Workers Union.; National Association of Letter Carriers (U.S.); National Post Office Mail Handlers.; United States Postal Service. Eastern Region.
5699389
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Issue: Absences--Sick-leave
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Rochester, NY, Branch 210, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Issue: Discipline--Suspensions
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch 286, Pittsfield, Massachusetts, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Issue: Discipline--Suspensions. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- USPS, West Springfield, Massachusetts vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch 1978, West Springfield, Massachusetts, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Issue: Discipline--Suspensions. RC.
- USPS, Rochester, New York vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Rochester Branch, No. 210, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Added Duties. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- USPS, Richmond, Virginia vs. American Postal Workers Union, Richmond, Virginia, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Issue: Discipline--Off-Duty Conduct. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Richmond, Virginia vs. American Postal Workers Union, Richmond, Virginia, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Issue: Absences--Discipline; Discipline--Off-Duty Conduct. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, Maintenance Craft, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Issue: Alcoholism, Drinking, and Intoxication--Drinking on the Job. RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Issue: Discipline--Off-Duty Conduct. AO.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Issue: Termination of Employment--Inability. AO.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Los Angeles, California, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  NA, RC. Cancelled.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Richmond, Virginia, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Issue: Termination of Employment--Failure to Qualify for Promotion. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Issue: Fights and Altercations--Assault on Supervisor. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- USPS, Buffalo, New York vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Buffalo, New York, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Issue: Negligence and Carelessness--Employee Liability. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- USPS vs. National Post Office Mail Handlers, Watchmen, Messengers and Group Leaders, Local No. 309, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Issue: Insubordination--Verbal Misconduct; Failure to Obey Orders. RC. (Jensen withdrew, award of other arbitrator included.)
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Issue: Transfers--Disciplinary Transfers. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Clerk Craft, Eastern Region, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Issue: Termination of Employment--Discrimination. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Issue: Insubordination--Discipline. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Mode of Dress; Improper Job Attitude--Leaving Plant or Work Area Without Permission. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Issue: Termination of Employment--Probationary Employees. AO.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Issue: Absences--Proof of Illness. AO.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Theft. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  NA, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Keystone Area Local, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct- -Sabotage. TR, EX, AN, RC, SD.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Issue: Absences--Falsification of Report. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Issue: Falsification--Applications for Employment. AO.
- USPS vs. Richmond, Virginia Local, American Postal Workers Union, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- USPS vs. Branch 157, National Association of Letter Carriers, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Issue: Fights and Altercations--Threats. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Issue: Fights and Altercations--Determining the Aggressor. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Issue: Physical Disability--Termination of Employment Following. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Issue: Negligence and Carelessness--Neglect of Duty. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Issue: Negligence and Carelessness--Discipline. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Issue: Theft--Suspicion. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Sabotage. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Issue: Fights and Altercations--Assault on Supervisor. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Issue: Testing of Employees--Training and Trial Periods. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  RC, NA. Settled.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Issue: Grievance and Grievance Procedure--Timeliness. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Post Office Mail Handlers, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Issue: Termination of Employment--Following Illness or Physical Disability. AO.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Intoxication. AO.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Issue: Falsification--Applications for Employment. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Woodbury, New Jersey, Branch 908, South Jersey Letter Carriers, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Issue: Discipline--Refusal to Return to Work. AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  RC, NA. Withdrawn.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Issue: Termination of Employment--Improper Personal Conduct. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch 84, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  2 Cases, Issues: Discipline--Basis; ii) Tardiness-- Discipline. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive; Discipline. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Issue: Negligence and Carelessness--Neglect of Duty; Insubordination--Failure to Obey Orders. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Issue: Theft--Company Property. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. Washington, D.C. Local, American Postal Workers Union and USPS, Eastern Region vs. Northern Virginia Facility Local, American Postal Workers Union, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Issue: Negotiations--Definitions. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Issue: Insubordination--Failure to Obey Orders. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia Local, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  Issue: Discipline--Excessive. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. Branch 210, National Association of Letter Carriers, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive; Falsification of Report. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Rochester Sectional Center Area Local, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. Mail Handlers Union, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Issue: Fights and Altercations--Assault on Fellow Employee. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Philadelphia Branch 157, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Discipline. TR, EX, LD, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Issue: Absences--Excuses. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch 84, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Issue: Fights and Altercations--Threats. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Issue: Testing of Employees--Training and Trial Periods. TR, EX. AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia Local, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Issue: Falsification--Medical Evidence. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Issue: Discipline--Leaving Plant Without Permission. AO.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. Erie Area Local, American Postal Workers Union, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Issue: Negotiations--Definitions. AO.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. Rochester Branch, No. 210, National Association of Letter Carriers, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Issue: Improper Job Attitude--Neglect of Duty; Loafing. AO.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia Local, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Issue: Theft--Intent. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  RC, NA.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Keystone Branch No. 157, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive; Excuses. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia Local, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Keystone Area Local, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Issue: Suspensions--Pending Court Action. AO.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive Excused Absences. AO.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Keystone Branch, No. 157, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive. AO.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Issue: Theft--Employee Liability for Robbery. AO.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive. RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, John F. Kennedy Memorial Branch No. 375, Utica, New York, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Richmond, Virginia, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Post Office Mail Handlers, Watchmen, Messengers and Group Leaders Division of the Laborer's International, Local No. 308, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Issue: Alcoholism, Drinking and Intoxication--Events Subsequent to Discharge; Fights and Altercations--Assault on Fellow Employee. AO.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Rochester, New York, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Issue: Falsification--Application for Employment. AO.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. Keystone Branch 157, National Association of Letter Carriers, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  2 Awards, 2 Issues: i) Insubordination--Failure to Obey Orders. ii) Tardiness--Excessive. AO.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch 732, Moorestown, New Jersey, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Issue: Suspension--Pending Court Action. RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  Issue: Strikes, Slowdowns, and Work Stoppages--Walkout; Union Representative. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Keystone Area Local, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Issue: Grievance and Grievance Procedure--Timeliness. RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Issue: Theft--Employee Liability for Robbery. RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Issue: Suspensions--Pending Court Action. RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Issue: Contracts--Contract Modification. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  Issue: Tardiness--Excessive. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  Issue: Suspensions--Pending Court Action. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Syracuse, New York, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Issue: Negligence and Carelessness--Neglect of Duty. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Qualifications; Overtime--Seniority. TR, EX, AN, RC, A.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  Issue: Theft--Company Property. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Bux-Mont Branch No. 920, Southampton, Pennsylvania, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  Issue: Testing of Employees--Ability. TR, EX, AN, RC, SD.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive. NA, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  Issue: Fights and Altercations--Provocation. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  Issue: Physical Disability--Termination of Employment Following. EX, AN, RC, SD.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch 258, Reading, Pennsylvania, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  Issue: Theft--Suspicion. EX, AN, RC, SD.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Huntington, West Virginia, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  Issue: Theft--Pilfering.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Tampering. EX, RC, AN.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  Issue: Improper Job Attitude--Insubordination. EX, RC, AN.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Rochester, New York, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  Issue: Reduction in Force--Assignment of Jobs. TR, EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  NA, RC. Settled.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Culpepper, Virginia, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  Issue: Negligence and Carelessness--Employee Liability. EX, AN, RC, SD.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  NA, RC. Withdrawn.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  Issue: Fights and Altercations--Verbal Assaults. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Keystone Branch No. 157, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  Issue: Absences--Proof of Illness; Negligence and Carelessness--Neglect of Duty. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. Mail Handlers Union, Local 322, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Off-Duty Misconduct. EX, AN, RC, SD.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Annapolis Local, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Issue: Theft--Company Product. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Association of Post Office Mail Handlers, Watchmen, Messengers, and Group Leaders, Division of LIUNA, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Baltimore, Maryland, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive; Termination of Employment-- Inability. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Washington, D.C., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Washington, D.C., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Richmond, Virginia, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Issue: Physical Disability--Termination of Employment Following. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Prince Georges, Riverdale, Maryland, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Issue: Absences--Alcoholism, Drinking, and Intoxication. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Northern Virginia Area Local, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Indecent Conduct. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Post Office Mail Handlers, Division of LIUNA, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Post Office Mail Handlers, Division of LIUNA, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Issue: Insubordination--Failure To Obey Orders; Verbal Misconduct. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Baltimore, Maryland, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Issue: Promotions--Failure To Qualify; Absences-- Excessive. EX, AN, RC, SD.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Pittsburgh Metro Area, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Issue: Holiday Work--Schedules of Work. EX, AN, RC, A.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Issue: Theft--Intent. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Post Office Mail Handlers, Division of LIUNA, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Issue: Fights and Altercations--Assault on Fellow Employee. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Keystone Branch No. 157, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  Issue: Negligence and Carelessness--Neglect of Duty; Absences--Excuses. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Pittsburgh Metro Area Local, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  Issue: Falsification--Application for Employment. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Maintenance Craft, Northern Virginia, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  Issue: Absences--Excessive; Alcoholism, Drinking, and Intoxication--Absences. EX, AN, RC.
- Maps for Buffalo, New York snow case (Box 5, Folder 21)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Wilmington, Delaware Local, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Issue: Theft Suspicion; Negligence and Carelessness--Carelessness. EX, AN, RC, SD.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, South Jersey, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Issue: Falsification--Application for Employment; Fights and Altercations--Assault by Outside Party. EX, AN, RC, SD.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia Area Local, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia Area Local, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Pennsylvania State Local, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Issue: Theft--Pilfering. EX, AN, RC, SD.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch 210, Rochester, New York, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Issue: Negligence and Carelessness-- Neglect of Duty. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, South Jersey Area Local 526, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Branch 258, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Issue: Falsification--Application for Employment. EX, AN, RC, SD.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, South Jersey Facility, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Issue: Shutdown--Weather Conditions. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Philadelphia Area Local, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Insubordination. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Post Office Mail Handlers, Division of LIUNA, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Issue: Grievance and Grievance Procedure-- Timeliness. EX, AN, RC, A.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, Rochester Branch No. 210, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Crossing Craft Lines. EX, AN, RC.
- USPS, Eastern Region vs. American Postal Workers Union, Buffalo, New York Local, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 15)